<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Blood Donor Checklist</string>
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to Blood Donor Checklist App!</string>
    <string name="quiz_explain">The following quiz access the availability to donate blood based on your honest answers to the questions.</string>
    <string name="quiz_time">There are 15 questions and it might take you around 10 minutes to complete the whole questionnaire. When you are ready, tap on \"Start Quiz\" button.</string>
    <string name="start_quiz">Start Quiz</string>
    <string name="quiz_1">1(a). Is your purpose for this donation visit to find out whether or not you are infected with HIV or suffering from AIDS?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="quiz_2">1(b). There is a window period in the early stage of HIV infection where you may test negative for the virus and you may feel well. Do you know that during this window period you can transmit the virus to someone else?</string>
    <string name="quiz_3">1(c). Is there any reason for you to suspect that you have or could possibly have been infected with HIV or AIDS?</string>
    <string name="quiz_4">1(d). Have you ever offered to anyone sexual activity* services for cash or benefits of any kind?</string>
    <string name="button_next">Next</string>
    <string name="quiz_5">2(a). Are you male or female?</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="quiz_6">2(a). Have you ever engaged in sexual activity* with another male?</string>
    <string name="quiz_7">2(b). In the past twelve (12) months, have you engaged in sexual activity* with a male whom you know or suspect to have engaged in sexual activity* with another male?</string>
    <string name="quiz_8">3(a). In the past twelve (12) months, have you had: unexplained weight loss or persistent night sweats, fever, diarrhoea or swollen glands?</string>
    <string name="quiz_9">3(b). In the last twelve (12) months, have you engaged in sexual activity* with anyone you know or have reason to suspect is infected with HIV or AIDS?</string>
    <string name="quiz_10">4. In the last twelve (12) months, have you:</string>
    <string name="quiz_11">(a)  received from anyone sexual activity* services for cash or benefits of any kind?</string>
    <string name="quiz_12">(b)  engaged in sexual activity* with anyone whom you have known for less than six (6) months?</string>
    <string name="quiz_13">(c)  engaged in sexual activity* with more than one partner?</string>
    <string name="quiz_14">(d)  had been diagnosed for syphilis, gonorrhea or any other sexually transmitted disease or had a positive test for syphilis?</string>
    <string name="quiz_15">(e)  engaged in sexual activity* with a person described as in paragraphs 4(a), (b), (c) or (d)? * \"sexual activity\" means: (a)\tsexual activity occasioned by the introduction into the vagina, anus or mouth of any person of any part of the penis of another person; or (b) cunnilingus.</string>
    <string name="quiz_16">5. Have you:</string>
    <string name="quiz_17">(a)  donated blood, double unit red cells, platelets or plasma in the last 16 weeks?</string>
    <string name="quiz_18">(b)  ever been told to stop giving blood or been refused as a blood donor?</string>
    <string name="quiz_19">(c)  ever had yellow jaundice or hepatitis or a positive hepatitis test?</string>
    <string name="quiz_20">(d)  been in close physical proximity with anyone with yellow jaundice or hepatitis or a positive hepatitis test in the past twelve (12) months?</string>
    <string name="quiz_21">(e)  ever received blood transfusion in UK, Mexico, France, South America and Central America or received plasma derived product in any country (including Singapore)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_22">(f)  received a blood transfusion in any other countries (other than the UK, Mexico, France, South America or Central America) in the last 12 months?</string>
    <string name="quiz_23">(g)  ever taken or been injected with addictive drugs?</string>
    <string name="quiz_24">(h)  within the past twelve (12) months, ever had body piercing (including ear piercing), tattoos, acupuncture done or been accidentally exposed to someone else\'s blood (including blood contaminated instrument)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_25">(i)  been detained or remanded in prison, approved institutions, approved homes or detention centers / barracks in the past twelve (12) months?</string>
    <string name="quiz_26">6(a). Are you feeling well today?</string>
    <string name="quiz_27">6(b). Do you have any fever today or during the past 3 weeks?</string>
    <string name="quiz_28">6(c). Do you understand the need to call back at once if you suspect your blood may carry infections that could be spread to patients or if you develop any symptoms of an infection (such as fever, rash, generalised body ache, sore throat, conjunctivitis, and persistent cough) in the first two weeks following blood donation?</string>
    <string name="quiz_29">7.  In the past twelve (12) months, have you:</string>
    <string name="quiz_30">(a)  been hospitalised?</string>
    <string name="quiz_31">(b)  been under a doctor\'s care regularly?</string>
    <string name="quiz_32">(c)  had a major illness or surgery (including wisdom tooth extraction)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_33">(d)  contracted or been in close contact with contagious infection, e.g. Chickenpox, measles, dengue, Chikungunya or any other viral infections?</string>
    <string name="quiz_34">8. Have you ever received / are taking:</string>
    <string name="quiz_35">(a)  Human Growth Hormone?</string>
    <string name="quiz_36">(b)  cornea / dura mater transplant?</string>
    <string name="quiz_37">(c)  insulin / diabetic medication?</string>
    <string name="quiz_38">9. In the past three (3) days, have you :</string>
    <string name="quiz_39">(a)  taken any medication (including pain killers)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_40">(b)  had a tooth extraction or dental work?</string>
    <string name="quiz_41">(c)  taken any form of traditional medicine (including herbal extract)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_42">10. Have you ever had:</string>
    <string name="quiz_43">(a)  heart trouble, chest pain, shortness of breath, persistent cough?</string>
    <string name="quiz_44">(b)  high blood pressure requiring medication?</string>
    <string name="quiz_45">(c)  Disease of the lungs, kidneys, liver or blood?</string>
    <string name="quiz_46">(d)  a diagnosis of any cancer?</string>
    <string name="quiz_47">(e)  any skin infection?</string>
    <string name="quiz_48">(f)  fainting, unconsciousness, fits or mental disorder?</string>
    <string name="quiz_49">(g)  Malaria, Babesiosis or Chagas Disease?</string>
    <string name="quiz_50">11  Have you received:</string>
    <string name="quiz_51">(a)  Any Hepatitis vaccination before?</string>
    <string name="quiz_52">When?</string>
    <string name="quiz_53">(b)  Any other injection or vaccination (other than hepatitis) in the past 12 months?</string>
    <string name="quiz_54">Please provide details of injection(s)/vaccination(s)</string>
    <string name="quiz_55">(c)  In the past eight weeks, have you received smallpox vaccination or have you had close physical contact with (eg, touch) the vaccination site of anyone who received small pox vaccination?</string>
    <string name="quiz_56">12(a). Are you currently pregnant?</string>
    <string name="quiz_57">12(b). Female Donors: Have you ever been pregnant in the past or had an abortion or a miscarriage previously?</string>
    <string name="quiz_58">12(c). If so, please provide the number and last date of pregnancy</string>
    <string name="quiz_59">13(a). In the past twelve (12) months, have you travelled out of Singapore?</string>
    <string name="quiz_60">If yes, where(Name of the country you visited)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_61">13(b). Have you ever lived in a malaria endemic area consecutively for 6 months or more?</string>
    <string name="quiz_62">Where?</string>
    <string name="quiz_63">13(c). Have you ever stayed in Mexico, South America or Central America for a continuous period of 4 weeks or more?</string>
    <string name="quiz_64">13(d). Have you visited or lived cumulatively in Europe for five (5) years or more from 1980 to the present, or the United Kingdom (England, Scotland, Wales, Northern Ireland, Isle of Man and Channel Islands) for three (3) months or more from 1980 to 1996?</string>
    <string name="quiz_65">13(e)  Do you have any immediate family members who has been diagnosed with Creutzfeld-Jacob Disease (CJD)?</string>
    <string name="quiz_66">14.  Do you understand that blood which is infected and donated to another person can cause disease, disability, pain, suffering and even death to him/her? Do you understand all the questions and information contained in this form and the donor information presented to you?</string>
    <string name="quiz_67">15.  Do you know that If you feel that your blood should not be transfused to another person, you can call the 24-hour hotline at telephone No. 1800-2263320 (Toll-Free) to alert HSA immediately.</string>
    <string name="quiz_68">When did you visit?</string>
</resources>
